I don't like to fly uh flying scares me
I have a friend that knows I don't like
to fly and he's always tried to convince
me with this he tells me that more
people are killed in automobile
accidents than there are in plane
crashes have you ever heard that okay
well that that might be true I ain't
never fail 30,000 ft out of my Buick um
which is another thing when I'm flying
why do they why do they feel the need to
tell me how high I am but you ever
notice that we'll be cruising at an
altitude of 38,000 ft well I really
don't care you know as long as we clear
the obstacles on the ground that's all I
care about you know that's like being on
a cruise ship I don't care how deep the
water is as long as we stay on
top they try to appease you with that on
the airplane they'll tell you they say
in the event of a water evacuation your
seat cushion will turn into a flotation
device
really why doesn't the plane turn into
to a boat how about that
huh my seat's going to float that's
supposed to make me feel better yeah
y'all know what dead bodies
float I'll grab me a fat guy and ride
him like a wave
runner too much crazy stuff going on out
there with airplanes I'll tell you I
bring this up I went to see this movie
recently uh that just came out called
Sully start Tom Hanks and it was about
that US Airways passenger jet that took
off from LaGuardia Airport and it flew a
flock of birds and they had to turn
around but they couldn't make it back to
LaGuardia and uh Sully sullenberger had
to land in the Hudson River do yall it
landed into the Hudson River how many of
y'all remember that photo up of the jet
floating on top of the river and all the
passengers were standing on the wings
waiting to be rescued yeah not one of
them was holding a seat
cushion I think I figured it out that's
probably the first thing you soil when
you find out you're going
now you're like I don't believe I'm
going to be taking that with
me well no ma'am it used to be
blue you guys should make the back of
the seat the
flotation